{"corefs": {"133": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "FINGERPRINTS\n\nBelgian police had found fingerprints belonging to Abdeslam at the scene of an apartment", "pos": ["NNS", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "131": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attack", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "130": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "night", "pos": ["NN"], "ner": ["TIME"]}], "137": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "136": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an apartment", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "135": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the scene of an apartment", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "134": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "fingerprints belonging to Abdeslam at the scene of an apartment", "pos": ["NNS", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "138": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "prosecutors", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "24": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Islamic State which claimed the attacks that killed 130 people", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Islamic State", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "25": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks that killed 130 people", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "26": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "130 people", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "20": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "French President Francois Hollande", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande, who was in Brussels for an EU summit", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "23": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "links to Syria and to Islamic State which claimed the attacks that killed 130 people", "pos": ["NNS", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "28": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "EU", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "EU", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "29": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The threat level", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "4": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The most-wanted fugitive from November's Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "8": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "police in Brussels", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "122": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Parisian", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "125": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "elder brother", "pos": ["JJR", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "himself", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "127": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Parisian cafe on Nov. 13", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CD"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE"]}], "128": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Nov. 13", "pos": ["NNP", "CD"], "ner": ["DATE", "DATE"]}], "59": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a sack on his head out of a building", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "58": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a man", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "54": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his congratulations", "pos": ["PRP$", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "57": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "armed security forces", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "56": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Television footage", "pos": ["NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "51": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the city", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "the city that", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "WDT"], "ner": ["O", "TIME", "TIME"]}], "50": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the other side of the city", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "53": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "U.S. President Barack Obama", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "52": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Europe's migration crisis", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "115": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his contacts in Europe and Syria", "pos": ["PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "114": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Islamic State plans and structures", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "117": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Europe and Syria", "pos": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "89": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "police officers", "pos": ["NNS", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "111": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Security services", "pos": ["NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "113": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam on Islamic State plans and structures", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "112": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Abdeslam on Islamic State plans and structures, his contacts in Europe and Syria and support networks and finance", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "82": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Several bursts of gunfire", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "83": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the capital's Molenbeek area - Abdeslam's home neighborhood and the scene of past investigations", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NNP", "NN", ":", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O"]}], "81": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "GMT", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "119": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "support networks", "pos": ["NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "87": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "past investigations", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O"]}], "84": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the capital's", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "85": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam's home neighborhood", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}], "3": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium's", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "7": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a shootout with police in Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "102": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the main police presence", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "103": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "crime scene investigators", "pos": ["NN", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "100": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the clear-up", "pos": ["DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "101": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Some four hours", "pos": ["DT", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "DATE", "DATE"]}], "107": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "speculation about whether Abdeslam had stayed in Belgium", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "39": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "bars and cafes", "pos": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "38": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a sports stadium", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "32": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an EU summit", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "31": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels for an EU summit", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "37": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "a sports stadium, bars and cafes and concert hall", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "NN", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "35": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "many more people", "pos": ["JJ", "JJR", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "60": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his head out", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "62": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a building", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "63": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a car", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "66": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgian government minister Theo Francken", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "67": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Twitter", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "69": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "France", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "2": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "6": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "November's", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O"]}], "99": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a new operation", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "98": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "a new operation or the clear-up", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "91": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "around 4 p.m. (1500 GMT)", "pos": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "-LRB-", "CD", "NNP", "-RRB-"], "ner": ["O", "TIME", "TIME", "O", "DATE", "MISC", "O"]}], "90": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an apartment block", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "92": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "1500 GMT", "pos": ["CD", "NNP"], "ner": ["DATE", "MISC"]}], "95": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the arrest", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "94": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Two explosions", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "97": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "part of a new operation or the clear-up", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "11": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Charles Michel", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "10": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgium's prime minister", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "13": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "two", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Two", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "12": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam, who was born and raised in Brussels to a Moroccan immigrant family", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam's", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam, whose elder brother blew himself up at a Parisian cafe on Nov. 13", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "WP$", "JJR", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CD"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "15": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam and two others as \"a very important result in the battle for democracy\"", "pos": ["JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "''"], "ner": ["DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "14": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam and two others as \"a very important result in the battle for democracy\"", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "''"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "17": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the battle for democracy", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "16": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a very important result in the battle for democracy", "pos": ["DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "19": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "130", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "18": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Syria", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Syria", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Syria", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "48": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the operation launched as EU leaders met on the other side of the city to discuss Europe's migration crisis", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "49": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "EU leaders", "pos": ["NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "86": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the scene of past investigations", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O"]}], "44": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europe's", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europe", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "45": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "local media", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "40": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "concert hall", "pos": ["NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "118": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "support networks and finance", "pos": ["NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "1": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "5": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "November's Paris attacks", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "9": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "77": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an operation mounted by Syria-based Islamic State in which all the known attackers died", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "76": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "more clarity", "pos": ["JJR", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "74": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Moroccan immigrant family", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "73": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels to a Moroccan immigrant family", "pos": ["NNP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "71": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Syria-based", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "78": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "47": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the leg", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}]}, "sentences": [{"openie": [{"object": "Brussels", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "police"}, {"object": "prime minister", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["LOCATION"]}, "subject": "Belgium"}, {"object": "police in Brussels", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "shootout"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "from", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["DATE"]}, "subject": "November"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as very important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "important result"}, {"object": "capture of Salah Abdeslam as important result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as result", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "26-year-old", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is of", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Salah Abdeslam"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old suspect Salah Abdeslam as very important result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of French Salah Abdeslam as result in battle", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "capture of 26-year-old French suspect Salah Abdeslam as important result in battle for democracy", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "``", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Charles Michel"}, {"object": "French", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is of", "ner": {"object": ["MISC"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Salah Abdeslam"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "French", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["MISC"], "relation": ["MISC"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Francois Hollande"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "involved in Paris attacks on sports stadium", "pos": {"object": ["VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "many more people"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been involved in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "many more people"}, {"object": "sports stadium", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "NN"], "relation": ["VBN", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been involved on", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more people"}, {"object": "involved", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more people"}, {"object": "sports stadium", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "NN"], "relation": ["VBN", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been involved on", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "many more people"}, {"object": "realized", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "been", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "it"}, {"object": "involved", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "many more people"}, {"object": "now clear", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "JJ"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "it"}, {"object": "involved in Paris attacks on sports stadium", "pos": {"object": ["VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more people"}, {"object": "clear", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "it"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been involved in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more people"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "migration crisis", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["LOCATION"]}, "subject": "Europe"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "his congratulations", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "sent", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "U.S. President Barack Obama"}, {"object": "U.S.", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is President of", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Barack Obama"}, {"object": "U.S.", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["LOCATION"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Barack Obama"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "armed security forces", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "showed", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Television footage"}, {"object": "sack on his head of building", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "armed security forces"}, {"object": "sack of building", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "armed security forces"}, {"object": "sack on his head", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}, {"object": "security forces", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "showed", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Television footage"}, {"object": "sack on his head out of building", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}, {"object": "sack on his head", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "armed security forces"}, {"object": "sack on his head out", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "armed security forces"}, {"object": "sack", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}, {"object": "man", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "armed security forces"}, {"object": "sack of building", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}, {"object": "sack on his head out", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}, {"object": "sack", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "armed security forces"}, {"object": "man", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}, {"object": "sack on his head of building", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}, {"object": "sack on his head out of building", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "dragging man with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "armed security forces"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Twitter", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "said on", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Belgian government minister Theo Francken"}, {"object": "Twitter", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "said on", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "government minister Theo Francken"}, {"object": "Belgian", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["JJ"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["MISC"], "relation": ["MISC"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Theo Francken"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Syria-based", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "is by", "ner": {"object": ["MISC"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}, "subject": "Islamic State"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "rang into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bursts"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "RB"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "rang out earlier into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bursts"}, {"object": "Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "capital"}, {"object": "around 4 p.m.", "pos": {"object": ["IN", "CD", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "surrounded apartment block there from", "ner": {"object": ["O", "TIME", "TIME"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police officers"}, {"object": "home neighborhood", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "capital 's Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "rang earlier in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Several bursts"}, {"object": "capital 's Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "rang in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bursts"}, {"object": "capital 's Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "RB"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "rang out earlier in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bursts"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "rang earlier into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Several bursts"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "RB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "rang out earlier into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Several bursts"}, {"object": "capital 's Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "RB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "rang out earlier in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Several bursts"}, {"object": "capital 's Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "rang earlier in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bursts"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "rang into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Several bursts"}, {"object": "around 4 p.m.", "pos": {"object": ["IN", "CD", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "surrounded apartment block from", "ner": {"object": ["O", "TIME", "TIME"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police officers"}, {"object": "apartment block", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "surrounded there", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police officers"}, {"object": "capital 's Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "rang in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Several bursts"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "rang earlier into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bursts"}, {"object": "apartment block", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "surrounded", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police officers"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "heard", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "explosions"}, {"object": "arrest", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["CD", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard after", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O"]}, "subject": "Two explosions"}, {"object": "arrest", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard after", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "explosions"}, {"object": "heard", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["CD", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O"]}, "subject": "Two explosions"}, {"object": "new operation", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "NN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "were part of", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "they"}, {"object": "part", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "they"}, {"object": "unclear", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "it"}, {"object": "operation", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "NN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "were part of", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "they"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "still work", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police presence"}, {"object": "work", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police presence"}, {"object": "still work", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "main police presence"}, {"object": "work", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "main police presence"}, {"object": "work", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "later had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["DATE"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police presence"}, {"object": "work", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "later had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["DATE"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "main police presence"}, {"object": "still work", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "later had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["DATE"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "main police presence"}, {"object": "still work", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "IN", "NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "later had stood at", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["DATE"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police presence"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Belgium", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "had stayed in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Europe", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["PRP$", "NNS"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "his contacts"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": []}]}