{"corefs": {"216": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Bilal Hadfi, another of the attackers who blew himself up with a bomb vest near the French national stadium during the attacks", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "217": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "another of the attackers who blew himself up with a bomb vest near the French national stadium during the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "215": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "DNA traces of Bilal Hadfi, another of the attackers who blew himself up with a bomb vest near the French national stadium during the attacks", "pos": ["NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "212": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a large belt", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "213": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Bilal Hadfi", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "himself", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "210": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a drawing", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "211": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a person wearing a large belt", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "218": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attackers", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "133": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the way", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "91": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a 35-year-old Algerian living", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O"]}], "90": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed Belkaïd, a 35-year-old Algerian living", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O"]}], "138": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "130", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "24": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "EU leaders", "pos": ["NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "25": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the other side of the city", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "26": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the city", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "27": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Europe’s migration crisis", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "20": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the leg", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "21": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a second person", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "O"]}], "22": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the operation, which took place as EU leaders met on the other side of the city to discuss Europe’s migration crisis", "pos": ["DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the operation", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the operation", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "95": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Kalashnikov", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "28": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "François Hollande", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "29": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Charles Michel", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "94": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "2014", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "4": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "8": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a police raid", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the raid", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "96": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salafism", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "120": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Bataclan", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "121": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "investigators", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "we", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Investigators", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "122": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a man using the name Samir Bouzid had received the last text message sent by three of the Paris attackers before they staged a bloody gun attack on a rock gig at the Bataclan concert hall", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "123": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the name Samir Bouzid had received the last text message sent by three of the Paris attackers before they staged a bloody gun attack on a rock gig at the Bataclan concert hall", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "124": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the last text message sent by three of the Paris attackers before they staged a bloody gun attack on a rock gig at the Bataclan concert hall", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The message", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "125": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "three of the Paris attackers", "pos": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "three", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "127": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a bloody gun attack", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "128": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a rock gig", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "129": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Bataclan concert hall", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "58": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "two more explosions", "pos": ["CD", "JJR", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}], "55": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "third", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["ORDINAL"]}], "54": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "two", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Two", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "it", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "two", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "56": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "three hours after the raid began", "pos": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "51": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "a rooftop and a helicopter", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "53": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a helicopter", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "52": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a rooftop", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "199": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Abdeslam and other suspects", "pos": ["NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}], "198": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a house used by Abdeslam and other suspects in the run-up to the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "194": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian authorities", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Authorities", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "197": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "two flats", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "196": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "two flats and a house used by Abdeslam and other suspects in the run-up to the attacks", "pos": ["CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "193": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "January", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "88": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one of the gunmen", "pos": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O"]}], "89": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a window: Mohamed Belkaïd, a 35-year-old Algerian living", "pos": ["DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O"]}], "110": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "112": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Samir Bouzid", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Samir Bouzid", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "83": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the door with automatic weapons", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "86": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "87": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A police sniper", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "84": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "automatic weapons", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "85": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed Belkaïd", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belkaïd", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "140": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a 26-year-old French national who grew up in Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "WP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "141": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "car hours", "pos": ["NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION"]}], "3": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "7": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "92": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "police over a theft case in 2014", "pos": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}], "102": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a Kalashnikov", "pos": ["DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC"]}], "103": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a book on Salafism and an Islamic State flag", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "101": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a Kalashnikov, a book on Salafism and an Islamic State flag,”", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "''"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "106": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Thierry Werts, of the Belgian federal prosecutor’s office", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "107": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian federal prosecutor’s office", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The Belgian prosecutor’s office", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}], "104": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Salafism and an Islamic State flag", "pos": ["NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "105": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an Islamic State flag", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "39": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "gunfire in Molenbeek", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "38": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "several exchanges of gunfire in Molenbeek – the scene of past investigations", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O"]}], "33": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian prime minister", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "32": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The French president", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O"]}], "31": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "The French president, François Hollande, and the Belgian prime minister", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "30": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "The French president, François Hollande, and the Belgian prime minister, Charles Michel", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "34": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the summit to discuss the operation", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "60": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian media", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}], "61": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a third man", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORDINAL", "O"]}], "64": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The police operation", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "65": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian prosecutors", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}], "66": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam’s fingerprints", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the fingerprints", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "67": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a flat that was raided in the Forest area of Brussels on Tuesday", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "DT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "DATE"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the flat", "pos": ["DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the flat", "pos": ["DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "68": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Forest area of Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "69": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "174": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris hours", "pos": ["NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "DURATION"]}], "172": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "friends", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "182": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s ID", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O"]}], "180": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the car", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "181": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the border", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "187": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a flat in the Schaerbeek district in north Brussels for three weeks", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "184": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the run", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "6": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A suspect in the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam, a 26-year-old French national who grew up in Brussels", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "WP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "His", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "188": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Schaerbeek district in north", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "189": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "three weeks", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "221": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the French national stadium", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "97": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Islamic", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "185": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Schaerbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "99": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his body", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "98": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Thierry Werts", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "168": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Paris bar", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "164": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Boulevard Voltaire", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "165": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "His brother", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "himself", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "93": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a theft case in 2014", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}], "224": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "this report", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "223": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Reuters", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "161": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the 18th arrondissement of the French capital", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "162": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the French capital", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O"]}], "220": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a bomb vest near the French national stadium", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "11": [{"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "10": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a four-month international manhunt", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION", "O", "O"]}], "13": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian secretary of state for asylum and migration", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "15": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "asylum and migration", "pos": ["NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "14": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "state for asylum and migration", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "17": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europe’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}], "16": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "EU", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "19": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the 26-year-old", "pos": ["DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION"]}], "18": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Police", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Police", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "themselves", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "143": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "130 people", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "117": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Le Monde", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "116": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the false name of Samir Bouzid", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "151": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the three suicide bombers who blew themselves up at the Stade de France as part of the coordinated assault", "pos": ["DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "153": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Stade de France", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "155": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the coordinated assault", "pos": ["DT", "VBN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "154": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "part of the coordinated assault", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "156": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "18th", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["ORDINAL"]}], "159": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his own suicide attack", "pos": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "48": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a street", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "49": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Reporters at the scene", "pos": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "46": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "black-clad security forces", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "47": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "balaclavas", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "44": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an apartment block", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "45": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Television footage", "pos": ["NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "43": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "police officers", "pos": ["NNS", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "40": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the scene of past investigations", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the scene", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "41": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "past investigations", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O"]}], "1": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "5": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A suspect in the Paris attacks, Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "9": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Molenbeek area of Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the area", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "201": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the run-up", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "200": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "other suspects", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "142": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the 13 November attacks that killed 130 people", "pos": ["DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "204": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "207": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "explosives, possible suicide belts and a drawing", "pos": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "206": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "traces of explosives, possible suicide belts and a drawing of a person wearing a large belt", "pos": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "209": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "possible suicide belts", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "208": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "explosives", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "148": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a key role", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "149": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the logistics of the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "75": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A Belgian federal prosecutor", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian federal prosecutor’s", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The Belgian prosecutor’s", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "74": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A Belgian federal prosecutor, Eric van der Sypt", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "FW", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "72": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Eric van der Sypt", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "FW", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "71": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Two suspects", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "79": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "French and Belgian police", "pos": ["JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "205": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A fingerprint belonging to Abdeslam", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}]}, "sentences": [{"openie": [{"object": "has shot in police raid after four-month manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area after four-month manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area after international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area after manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area after four-month international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area after four-month international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area of Brussels after manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area of Brussels after manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot after international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area of Brussels after international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area after international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area of Brussels after four-month manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid after four-month international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area after four-month manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid after international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area of Brussels", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot after four-month manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area of Brussels", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area of Brussels after four-month international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid after manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area of Brussels after four-month international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot after four-month international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid in Molenbeek area after manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area of Brussels after international manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in Molenbeek area of Brussels after four-month manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot after manhunt", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}, {"object": "has shot in police raid", "pos": {"object": ["VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspect"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "him", "pos": {"object": ["PRP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "got", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "We"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "migration crisis", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["LOCATION"]}, "subject": "Europe"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "minister", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "president"}, {"object": "summit", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "president"}, {"object": "François Hollande", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "president"}, {"object": "Belgian minister", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "French president"}, {"object": "Belgian prime minister", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "French president"}, {"object": "prime minister", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "French president"}, {"object": "François Hollande", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "French president"}, {"object": "summit", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "French president"}, {"object": "minister", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "French president"}, {"object": "Belgian minister", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "president"}, {"object": "prime minister", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "president"}, {"object": "Belgian prime minister", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "left", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "president"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "several exchanges"}, {"object": "apartment block", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NNS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "surrounding", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police officers"}, {"object": "apartment block", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NNS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "surrounding there", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police officers"}, {"object": "Molenbeek", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "gunfire"}, {"object": "Paris attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "were into", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "exchanges"}, {"object": "seen", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police officers"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "balaclavas", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "wearing", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "black-clad security forces"}, {"object": "black-clad security forces", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "showed", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Television footage"}, {"object": "security forces", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "showed", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "Television footage"}, {"object": "balaclavas", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "wearing", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "security forces"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "smoke rising", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "VBG"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Reporters"}, {"object": "white smoke rising", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "VBG"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Reporters"}, {"object": "smoke", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Reporters"}, {"object": "smoke rising from rooftop", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Reporters"}, {"object": "white smoke", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Reporters"}, {"object": "white smoke rising from rooftop", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "described", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Reporters"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "About three hours heard in area", "pos": {"object": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more explosions"}, {"object": "three hours raid began", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard About", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more explosions"}, {"object": "three hours", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard About", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more explosions"}, {"object": "About three hours began heard in area", "pos": {"object": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more explosions"}, {"object": "area", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["CD", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard in", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "two more explosions"}, {"object": "heard", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["CD", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "two more explosions"}, {"object": "heard", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more explosions"}, {"object": "three hours raid began", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["CD", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard About", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "two more explosions"}, {"object": "area", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard in", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more explosions"}, {"object": "About three hours heard in area", "pos": {"object": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["CD", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "two more explosions"}, {"object": "three hours", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["CD", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were heard About", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "two more explosions"}, {"object": "About three hours began heard in area", "pos": {"object": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["CD", "JJR", "NNS"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "two more explosions"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Forest area of Brussels", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["DT"]}, "relation": "was raided in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "that"}, {"object": "raided", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["DT"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "that"}, {"object": "Forest area", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["DT"]}, "relation": "was raided in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "that"}, {"object": "raided in Forest area on Tuesday", "pos": {"object": ["VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["DT"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "that"}, {"object": "launched", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police operation"}, {"object": "Tuesday", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["DT"]}, "relation": "was raided on", "ner": {"object": ["DATE"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "that"}, {"object": "found", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNP", "POS", "NNS"]}, "relation": "been", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam 's fingerprints"}, {"object": "fingerprints", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "raided in Forest area of Brussels on Tuesday", "pos": {"object": ["VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["DT"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "that"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "raid", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "fled that", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "suspects"}, {"object": "raid", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["CD", "NNS"]}, "relation": "fled that", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["NUMBER", "O"]}, "subject": "Two suspects"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "fired", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "were", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "they"}, {"object": "Belgian police", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["JJ"]}, "relation": "search", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC"]}, "subject": "French"}, {"object": "automatic weapons", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["IN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN"]}, "relation": "is with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "at from door"}, {"object": "Belgian police", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ"]}, "relation": "arrived", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC"]}, "subject": "French"}, {"object": "police", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ"]}, "relation": "arrived", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC"]}, "subject": "French"}, {"object": "police", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["JJ"]}, "relation": "search", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC"]}, "subject": "French"}, {"object": "flat", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["JJ"]}, "relation": "search", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC"]}, "subject": "French"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "police", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBN", "TO"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "known to", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police sniper"}, {"object": "one of gunmen", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "shot", "ner": {"object": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police sniper"}, {"object": "police over theft case in 2014", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD"], "relation": ["VBN", "TO"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "known to", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police sniper"}, {"object": "one gunmen", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "shot", "ner": {"object": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police sniper"}, {"object": "police over theft case", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBN", "TO"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "known to", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "police sniper"}, {"object": "2014", "pos": {"object": ["CD"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "theft case"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "office", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "of", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Belgian federal prosecutor"}, {"object": "book on Salafism", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG", "TO"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "according to Kalashnikov is", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Thierry Werts"}, {"object": "Salafism", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NN", "IN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "book on", "ner": {"object": ["MISC"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC"]}, "subject": "Kalashnikov"}, {"object": "book on Salafism", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["JJ", "TO"], "subject": ["PRP$", "NN"]}, "relation": "Next to Kalashnikov is", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "his body"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "office", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "Belgian prosecutor"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "way", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBP", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "'re on", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "we"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "car hours", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "NNP"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "fled Paris by", "ner": {"object": ["O", "DURATION"], "relation": ["O", "LOCATION"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "car hours", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "fled by", "ner": {"object": ["O", "DURATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "Paris", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "fled", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "Belgium", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "NNP"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "fled Paris for", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O", "LOCATION"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "Belgium", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "fled for", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "Boulevard Voltaire", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP$", "NN"]}, "relation": "died on", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "His brother"}, {"object": "attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP$", "NN"]}, "relation": "died during", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "His brother"}, {"object": "Paris bar", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP$", "NN"]}, "relation": "died at", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "His brother"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "him", "pos": {"object": ["PRP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "collect", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "friends", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "had called", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "allowed through", "pos": {"object": ["VBN", "IN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "checked", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam 's ID"}, {"object": "stopped", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "car"}, {"object": "allowed", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "run", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBN", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "been on", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "ID", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Abdeslam"}, {"object": "briefly stopped", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "car"}, {"object": "him", "pos": {"object": ["PRP"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBG"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "were driving", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "they"}, {"object": "run ever since", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "RB", "IN"], "relation": ["VBN", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "been on", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "him", "pos": {"object": ["PRP"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBG"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "were driving back", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "they"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "three weeks", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "is for", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["LOCATION"]}, "subject": "Brussels"}, {"object": "north", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, "subject": "Schaerbeek district"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "January", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "said In", "ner": {"object": ["DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "authorities"}, {"object": "January", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "said In", "ner": {"object": ["DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "Belgian authorities"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "traces of explosives of person", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "flat traces of person", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "one", "pos": {"object": ["CD"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found in", "ner": {"object": ["NUMBER"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "traces of person", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "flat traces of explosives of person", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "flat traces", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "found", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "traces of explosives", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "flat traces of explosives", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}, {"object": "traces", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBD", "VBN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was found along with", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "fingerprint"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "DNA traces of Bilal Hadfi", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "also found", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Authorities"}, {"object": "DNA traces", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "found", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Authorities"}, {"object": "attackers", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["DT", "IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "another of", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Bilal Hadfi"}, {"object": "DNA traces", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "also found", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Authorities"}, {"object": "DNA traces of Bilal Hadfi", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "found", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "Authorities"}]}, {"openie": []}]}