{"corefs": {"344": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the middle of a residential part of Molenbeek", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "345": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a residential part of Molenbeek", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "347": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ilias", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "342": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a fusillade of shots", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "343": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "shots", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "349": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "RTL", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "299": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "armed security forces", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "296": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "297": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "one point during the raid", "pos": ["CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "295": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian shepherds", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}], "292": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Europe’s migrant crisis", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "290": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday afternoon", "pos": ["NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["DATE", "TIME"]}], "291": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a landmark deal", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "199": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the final ones connected to the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "594": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "still not said exactly how many people may have been involved in the plot, or exactly how it originated", "pos": ["RB", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "599": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The failure of Belgian authorities to notice the November terrorist attacks being plotted in their midst — followed by their failure to promptly apprehend Abdeslam —", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ":"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O"]}], "194": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "two of them", "pos": ["CD", "IN", "PRP"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}], "197": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Friday’s raids", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O", "O"]}], "196": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Both leaders", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "we", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "192": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "three people", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "those people", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "270": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an ongoing operation", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "271": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "273": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A shootout", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "274": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "275": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the death of one suspect and the wounding of four Belgian police officers", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "276": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the death of one suspect", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "277": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "one suspect", "pos": ["CD", "NN"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "278": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the wounding of four Belgian police officers", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "279": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "four Belgian police officers", "pos": ["CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "525": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the last couple of months", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "527": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "smoking and drinking", "pos": ["NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "521": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "mass murder", "pos": ["NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "522": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "a Muslim who prays, had in the last couple of months stopped smoking and drinking, and goes to the mosque once in a while", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "528": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the mosque once in a while", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O"]}], "529": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a while", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "449": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam at a gas station in Ressons, France", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "443": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ressons", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "442": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "30", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "440": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "89 people", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "447": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Another suspect", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed Abrini, 30", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed Abrini", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abrini", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abrini, a Belgian national of North African origin", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abrini", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "446": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Another suspect, Mohamed Abrini, 30", "pos": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER"]}], "108": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a fake Syrian passport, van der Sypt", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "FW", "FW"], "ner": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "109": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a fake Syrian passport", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "100": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The fifth person", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORDINAL", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hadj", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "101": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Brussels hospital", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "106": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Thursday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "107": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Forest district of Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "105": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "separate raids Thursday in the Forest district of Brussels", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the raids in Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "38": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "officials", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "33": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "reporters", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "reporters", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "31": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the spokesman, Eric van der Sypt", "pos": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "FW", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the spokesman", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the spokesman", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "30": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "One of the four, identified as Monir Ahmed al-Hadj", "pos": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "36": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the leg", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "35": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a 26-year-old French national", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION", "MISC", "O"]}], "641": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Bart de Wever", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "640": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Antwerp", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "438": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Bataclan concert hall, where 89 people were massacred", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O"]}], "439": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Bataclan concert hall", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O"]}], "436": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "89", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "437": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a car in Belgium that was later found near the Bataclan concert hall, where 89 people were massacred", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O"]}], "435": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Bataclan", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "432": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an American rock band", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "430": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a concert hall during a performance by an American rock band", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "431": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a performance by an American rock band", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "339": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Witnesses to the raid", "pos": ["NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "334": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Theo Francken, Belgium’s secretary of state for asylum and migration", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "your", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "337": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "asylum and migration", "pos": ["NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "336": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "state for asylum and migration", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "330": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Theo Francken", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgium’s secretary of state for asylum and migration", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "6": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "It", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "99": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The fifth person, Hadj", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "ORDINAL", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}], "91": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Belgian who may be behind the Paris attacks]\n\nVan der Sypt said the three Abdeslam relatives who were arrested Friday", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "-RRB-", "NNP", "FW", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}], "93": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the three Abdeslam relatives who were arrested Friday", "pos": ["DT", "CD", "NNP", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "NUMBER", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "relatives", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "92": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks, when French police stopped a car he was riding in near the Belgian border", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "96": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "fifth", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["ORDINAL"]}], "559": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Schaerbeek district of Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "558": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an apartment", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "554": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Schaerbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "557": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "January", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "550": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his whereabouts", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "553": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "recent weeks", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "552": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The hunt", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "238": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an investigation", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "239": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "some of the most basic details of the Paris attack plot, including where it was hatched", "pos": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "234": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Terrorism analysts", "pos": ["NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "237": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a turning point in an investigation that has so far failed to unearth some of the most basic details of the Paris attack plot, including where it was hatched and by whom", "pos": ["DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "WP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "232": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "France’s extradition request", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "1": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels, authorities", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "NNS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "146": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the result of close coordination between French and Belgian law enforcement", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "147": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "French and Belgian law enforcement", "pos": ["JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "us", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "618": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "six local police forces — not all of which speak the same language — as well as a federal police agency", "pos": ["CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ":", "RB", "DT", "IN", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "619": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the same language", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "142": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "this awful negation of human life", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "140": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a huge success in the battle", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "141": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the battle", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "612": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "ethnic lines", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "613": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "French-speaking, Dutch-speaking and German-speaking citizens", "pos": ["JJ", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "610": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The country", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "611": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "ethnic lines, where French-speaking, Dutch-speaking and German-speaking citizens live in an uneasy coexistence with each other", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "617": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "six", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "614": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an uneasy coexistence with each other", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "615": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "each other", "pos": ["DT", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "623": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Flemish", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Flemish", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "133": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the fight against terrorism", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "132": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "@POTUS Belgium and France", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "131": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Congratulations from @POTUS Belgium and France", "pos": ["NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "130": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Twitter", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Twitter", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Twitter", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "136": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a news conference Friday", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}], "134": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "@POTUS", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "494": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the case", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "139": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the arrests", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the arrests", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the arrests", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "138": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "evening", "pos": ["NN"], "ner": ["TIME"]}], "492": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "His co-defendant in the case", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a childhood friend, Abdelhamid Abaaoud, who would become the ringleader of the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a childhood friend", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdelhamid Abaaoud", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abaaoud", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "24": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian federal prosecutor’s office", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his office", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian prosecutor’s office", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}], "25": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian federal prosecutor’s", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian prosecutor’s", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "27": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Monir Ahmed al-Hadj", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "20": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "police", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Police", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "police", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "police", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Police", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "21": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "three raids over a four-hour operation", "pos": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "O"]}], "22": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a four-hour operation", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the operation", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "23": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a spokesman for the Belgian federal prosecutor’s office", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "28": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Eric van der Sypt", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "FW", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Van der Sypt", "pos": ["NNP", "FW", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "van der Sypt", "pos": ["NN", "FW", "FW"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "405": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the night of the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "TIME", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "night", "pos": ["NN"], "ner": ["TIME"]}], "404": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Boulevard Voltaire", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "401": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam’s older brother, Brahim Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "JJR", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "629": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium in its current form", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "DATE", "O"]}], "408": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a suicide mission that", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT"], "ner": ["O", "O", "TIME", "TIME"]}], "371": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the window", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "372": [{"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "374": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the curtains", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "377": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Rue", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "393": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "their midst", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "their midst", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "392": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the growing radicalization in their midst", "pos": ["DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "88": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "[", "pos": ["-LRB-"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a barbaric man", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "397": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "detonations", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "396": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "More than an hour after Abdeslam", "pos": ["JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "PERSON"]}], "82": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgium’s VTM television channel", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O"]}], "181": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the chance to know the whole truth", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "80": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgium’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "its", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "81": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "VTM", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "7": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam, a key suspect in last year’s bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "584": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an explosives belt that had been discarded in a Paris trash", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "585": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Paris trash", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "580": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "More than a week after the killings, authorities", "pos": ["JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "it", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "589": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "More than four months after the attacks, which were believed to have been planned in Brussels, authorities", "pos": ["JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O"]}], "245": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Jean-Charles Brisard, chairman of the Paris-based Center for the Analysis of Terrorism", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "247": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Paris-based Center for the Analysis of Terrorism", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "241": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris attack plot", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "it", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "240": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the most basic details of the Paris attack plot", "pos": ["DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O"]}], "243": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Jean-Charles Brisard", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "chairman of the Paris-based Center for the Analysis of Terrorism", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "249": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a role in virtually every stage of the planning and the preparation", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "518": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friends", "pos": ["NNPS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "our", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "511": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Another brother", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed Belkaid", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "510": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Another brother, Mohamed Abdeslam", "pos": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "514": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his wife", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "517": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Friends and relatives", "pos": ["NNPS", "CC", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "516": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "no children", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "458": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "European authorities", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}], "459": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europol", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the E.U.’s law enforcement agency", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "620": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a federal police agency", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "627": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "intelligence services", "pos": ["NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "626": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "intelligence services and counterterrorism", "pos": ["NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "624": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgium’s interior minister, Jan Jambon, who oversees intelligence services and counterterrorism", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "450": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a gas station in Ressons, France", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "451": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ressons, France", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "452": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the highway to Paris two days", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "453": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "two days", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "178": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Friday’s arrests", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Friday’s arrests", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O", "O"]}], "176": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "investigators", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "174": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "several attackers", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "us", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "173": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "rented apartments", "pos": ["VBN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "171": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "sites", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "rented cars", "pos": ["VBN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "170": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "sites, rented cars", "pos": ["NNS", ",", "VBN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "656": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Witte", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "182": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the whole truth", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "657": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "London", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "654": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his word", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "2": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a key suspect in last year’s bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam, a resident of the Molenbeek neighborhood of Brussels before the attacks", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a resident of the Molenbeek neighborhood of Brussels before the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam’s older brother", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "JJR", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brahim Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the most wanted man in Europe", "pos": ["DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam himself", "pos": ["NNP", "PRP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "himself", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "His", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "the 5-foot-7-inch Abdeslam", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Abdeslam", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "652": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Flemish nationalist party", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "187": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the site of the arrests", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "184": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Brussels operation", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "651": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the Flemish nationalist party and Antwerp Mayor Bart de Wever", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "658": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Birnbaum", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "653": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Antwerp Mayor Bart de Wever", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "650": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the leader of the Flemish nationalist party and Antwerp Mayor Bart de Wever", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "11": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a shootout that left him wounded", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "10": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "last year’s", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["DATE", "DATE", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "last year", "pos": ["JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["DATE", "DATE"]}], "13": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "European leaders", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}], "14": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Four", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "four", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "four", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "four", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "17": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Four other people", "pos": ["CD", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}], "19": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam’s family", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "our family", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "18": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "three of them members of Abdeslam’s family", "pos": ["CD", "IN", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "three", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "three", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "three", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Three", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "659": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Moscow", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "320": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel in his office", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}], "324": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "news of the raid", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "328": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Three senior European officials", "pos": ["CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "201": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the web of accomplices", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "203": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "authorities originally believed", "pos": ["NNS", "RB", "VBN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "202": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "accomplices", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "206": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "this attack", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attack", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "77": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "explosions", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "76": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the initial raid", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "75": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the initial raid, explosions", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "74": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hours after the initial raid, explosions", "pos": ["NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "the hours", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "72": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a massive manhunt across Europe", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "71": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "then", "pos": ["RB"], "ner": ["O"]}], "70": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "authorities since then", "pos": ["NNS", "IN", "RB"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "79": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "other suspected terrorists", "pos": ["JJ", "VBN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "78": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Brussels neighborhood", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "667": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "this report", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "666": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Frankfurt, Germany", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "665": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Washington and Souad Mekhennet in Frankfurt, Germany", "pos": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "664": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "William Branigin in Washington and Souad Mekhennet in Frankfurt, Germany", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "663": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Germany", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "662": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Frankfurt", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "661": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Washington", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "660": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "London and Birnbaum", "pos": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON"]}], "542": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "French police", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the police", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the police", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "543": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a car he was riding in near the Belgian border", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "545": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian border", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O"]}], "548": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the car to proceed", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "549": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the search for his whereabouts", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "68": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels before the attacks", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "120": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian security services", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O"]}], "121": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "this significant arrest", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "122": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the result of hard work and close cooperation between Belgian and French law enforcement authorities", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}], "123": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the result of hard work", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "124": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Belgian and French law enforcement authorities", "pos": ["JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian authorities", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "authorities", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "authorities", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "authorities", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "their", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "125": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the White House", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "126": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a statement", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "129": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "France", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "France", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "France’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "France", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "414": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Law enforcement officials", "pos": ["NN", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "416": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a change of heart", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "411": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "a French and Belgian dragnet", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "418": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "months", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "months", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION"]}], "311": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "E.U. leaders", "pos": ["NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "310": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a summit of E.U. leaders", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "317": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his ear", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "316": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a phone", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "315": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the 28-leader meeting", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "497": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the ringleader of the Paris attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "3": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paris", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "368": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a person", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "369": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the ground", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "364": [{"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "It", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "365": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "A dozen gunshots.", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "ner": ["O", "NUMBER", "O", "O"]}], "363": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "gunshots", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "gunshots", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "360": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "My son", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "381": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek’s Rue des Quatre-Vents", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Rue des Quatre-Vents", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "MISC", "MISC"]}], "382": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "less than four blocks from the area’s town hall", "pos": ["JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "383": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the area’s town hall", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "384": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the area’s", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "386": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a modest residence across a cobbled square", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "387": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a cobbled square", "pos": ["DT", "VBN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "388": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Molenbeek town hall, the seat of local authorities who have been criticized for doing little to monitor the growing radicalization in their midst", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "389": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Molenbeek town hall", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the seat of local authorities who have been criticized for doing little to monitor the growing radicalization in their midst", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "573": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the dead man", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "570": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a suspect with possible Islamic State ties", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "577": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam’s exact role in the plot", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "153": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the values of liberty", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "575": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a 35-year-old Algerian", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "DURATION", "MISC"]}], "574": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mohamed Belkaid, a 35-year-old Algerian", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "DURATION", "MISC"]}], "60": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The Islamic State terrorist group", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O"]}], "61": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the assault", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "259": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian federal prosecutors", "pos": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "they", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "67": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Molenbeek neighborhood of Brussels before the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Molenbeek neighborhood of Brussels", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "252": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the planning", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "69": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks, which were believed to have been planned in Brussels, authorities", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "250": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "virtually every stage of the planning and the preparation", "pos": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "251": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the planning and the preparation", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "256": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the masterminds behind the attack", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "255": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the missing link to the masterminds behind the attack", "pos": ["DT", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "506": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Paris suburb", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "504": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "French security forces on a hideout in a Paris suburb", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "505": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a hideout in a Paris suburb", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "502": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks in a raid", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "503": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a raid", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "501": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "five days", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "630": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "its current form", "pos": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "DATE", "O"]}], "469": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "at least 10 people suspected of involvement with Abdeslam", "pos": ["IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}], "636": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "French-speaking parts of the police and local government", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "637": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the police and local government", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "465": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Belgian national of North African origin", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "MISC", "MISC", "O"]}], "466": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "10", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "461": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europol, the E.U.’s law enforcement agency", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "169": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the killings", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the killings, authorities", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the killings", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "165": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the logistics chief", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "163": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam’s extradition", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O"]}], "9": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "last year’s bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "649": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a top ally", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "648": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a top ally, the leader of the Flemish nationalist party and Antwerp Mayor Bart de Wever", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "357": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a resident identified as Ilias", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}], "356": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "’” a resident identified as Ilias told Belgium’s RTL television", "pos": ["CD", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "355": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the air", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "353": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "your hands", "pos": ["PRP$", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "352": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a person to ‘put your hands in the air,’” a resident identified as Ilias told Belgium’s RTL television", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "``", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "I", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "My", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "I", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "me", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "351": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a megaphone", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "358": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgium’s RTL television", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "216": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Islamist", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "214": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "everyone connected with the “abomination” inflicted on Paris", "pos": ["NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "VBN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "215": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the “abomination” inflicted on Paris", "pos": ["DT", "``", "NN", "''", "VBN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "212": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the victims", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "213": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the arrest of everyone connected with the “abomination” inflicted on Paris", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "VBN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "211": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the families of the victims", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "218": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgian Interior Minister Jan Jambon", "pos": ["JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgium’s interior minister", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Jan Jambon", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Flemish nationalist who has questioned whether Belgium in its current form should exist at all", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Jambon", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Jambon", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "289": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the European Union", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "288": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the European Union, which on Friday afternoon announced a landmark deal with Turkey on Europe’s migrant crisis", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "TIME", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "4": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "PARIS — Belgian counterterrorism police raided an apartment block in Brussels on Friday and arrested Salah Abdeslam, a key suspect in last year’s bloody terrorist attacks in Paris, after a shootout that left him wounded, European leaders said.", "pos": ["NNP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europe", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europe", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europe’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Brussels on Friday", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Europe", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "281": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "European Union", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "282": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Turkey", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "284": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The raid on Friday", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the raid", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the raid", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the raid", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the raid", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Friday’s raid", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["DATE", "O", "O"]}], "287": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the headquarters of the European Union, which on Friday afternoon announced a landmark deal with Turkey on Europe’s migrant crisis", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "TIME", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O"]}], "286": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "4:45 p.m. local time in Molenbeek", "pos": ["CD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["TIME", "TIME", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "263": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one of Europe’s most wanted men", "pos": ["CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "VBD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "262": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the fingerprints of Abdeslam", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}], "261": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the fingerprints of Abdeslam, one of Europe’s most wanted men", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "VBD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "267": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "earlier this week", "pos": ["RBR", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE"]}], "265": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an apartment raided by police earlier this week", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "RBR", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE"]}], "264": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "men", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "269": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "further details", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "59": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one of his brothers", "pos": ["CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O", "O"]}], "58": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Seven other attackers", "pos": ["CD", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}], "55": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the scene", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "57": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Seven", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "56": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a suicide vest", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a suicide vest", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "51": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "13 attacks in Paris that killed 130 people and wounded at least 368 others", "pos": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "50": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Nov.", "pos": ["DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "DATE"]}], "53": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "at least 368 others", "pos": ["IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "52": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "130 people", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "537": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Law enforcement", "pos": ["NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Law enforcement", "pos": ["NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "63": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek,” which has earned a reputation as a hotbed of Islamist radicalism in Europe", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "''", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek’s", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Molenbeek", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "533": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a frustration that our family lived together without noticing what was going on", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "530": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the French channel BFMTV", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "538": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Salah Abdeslam in the hours", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "115": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "French President Francois Hollande", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "114": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "French President Francois Hollande and Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "them", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "116": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Belgian Prime Minister Charles Michel", "pos": ["JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel, the Belgian prime minister", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Michel", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Belgian prime minister", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "111": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Francois Hollande", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Hollande", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "113": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "President Obama", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Obama", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Obama, in the congratulatory call", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Obama", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "112": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the arrest of Abdeslam", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}], "119": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the work of Belgian security services", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "429": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "venues", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "428": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a variety of venues", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "423": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the continent", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "422": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Law enforcement agencies across the continent", "pos": ["NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "425": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "vital clues", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "424": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a man who could provide vital clues about the still-murky origins of a plot that spilled blood at a variety of venues across Paris, including a concert hall during a performance by an American rock band", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "427": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a plot that spilled blood at a variety of venues across Paris, including a concert hall during a performance by an American rock band", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the plot", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the plot", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "it", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "426": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the still-murky origins of a plot that spilled blood at a variety of venues across Paris, including a concert hall during a performance by an American rock band", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O"]}], "300": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a limping man", "pos": ["DT", "VBG", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "301": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a hoodie over his head out of an apartment building", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "302": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his head out", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "304": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an apartment building", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "307": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "E.U.", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "the E.U.’s", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "568": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Paris investigation", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "569": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "clashes that left a suspect with possible Islamic State ties dead", "pos": ["NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "JJ"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"]}], "560": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Abdeslam’s fingerprint", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O"]}], "562": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "French-Belgian", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "564": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Islamic", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "565": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday in Brussels", "pos": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["DATE", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "566": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a joint French-Belgian police operation that authorities said was linked to the Paris investigation", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "227": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a single person", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "226": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The jihadists", "pos": ["DT", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "225": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgium’s RTBF broadcaster", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "223": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "RTBF", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "221": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a reputation as a hotbed of Islamist radicalism in Europe", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "391": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "local authorities", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "their", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "151": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the congratulatory call", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "604": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "their failure to promptly apprehend Abdeslam", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}], "607": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "political factions", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "606": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a political embarrassment", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "601": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the November terrorist attacks being plotted in their midst", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "600": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Belgian authorities to notice the November terrorist attacks being plotted in their midst", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "their", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "157": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the “preparation, organization and perpetration” of the attacks on several civilian targets in Paris", "pos": ["DT", "``", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "''", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the preparation", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "159": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "several civilian targets in Paris", "pos": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "158": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the attacks on several civilian targets in Paris", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "609": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "German-speaking", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "608": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "French-speaking", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "French-speaking", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "83": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "another suspect", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "634": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the intelligence failures", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "48": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "part of a plan to participate in the Nov. 13 attacks in Paris that killed 130 people and wounded at least 368 others", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "49": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a plan to participate in the Nov. 13 attacks in Paris that killed 130 people and wounded at least 368 others", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "46": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a car", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a car", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "44": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "368", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "43": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "130", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "5": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an apartment block", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "489": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "2011", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "486": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his brother", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Café Les Beguines", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "485": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his brother, Café Les Beguines", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "484": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a local café owned by his brother, Café Les Beguines", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "480": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Moroccan immigrants", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}], "470": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Syria", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "477": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The Abdeslam brothers, the sons of Moroccan immigrants", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "478": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The Abdeslam brothers", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the sons of Moroccan immigrants", "pos": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}]}, "sentences": [{"openie": [{"object": "Paris", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBN", "NNP"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested Salah Abdeslam in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O", "PERSON"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "last year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["NN", "IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "suspect in", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Salah Abdeslam"}, {"object": "Paris", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBN", "NNP"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested Salah Abdeslam in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O", "PERSON"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["DATE", "DATE"]}, "subject": "last year"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in last year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "last year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "key suspect"}, {"object": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "Salah Abdeslam", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "suspect in year 's terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's bloody attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "European leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in last year 's attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "key suspect in year 's bloody terrorist attacks", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "arrested", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}]},