{"corefs": {"216": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his former rivals", "pos": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "215": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "this week", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["DATE", "DATE"]}], "212": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Florida Senator Marco Rubio", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "213": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Republican race", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O"]}], "211": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Florida Senator Marco Rubio, who left the Republican race on Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "DATE"]}], "132": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Mr Trump's other opponent, Ohio Governor John Kasich", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "131": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the knife in Mr Trump's other opponent, Ohio Governor John Kasich", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "130": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "this", "pos": ["DT"], "ner": ["O"]}], "137": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "His efforts", "pos": ["PRP$", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "165": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "behalf of the group", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "139": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the last round of voting", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "It", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "26": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "other Republican leaders coalescing around Mr Cruz", "pos": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Republican leaders", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Republican leaders", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["MISC", "O"]}], "20": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Governor John Kasich in Ohio", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Mr Trump's other opponent", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ohio Governor John Kasich", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "John Kasich", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "her opponent", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "21": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "voting for Mr Cruz", "pos": ["NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the only way to stop \"Trumpism\"", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "``", "FW", "''"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "22": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Cruz", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Cruz", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Cruz", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Cruz", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Cruz", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}], "95": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the 2012 Republican nominee, still highly respected among the state's large Mormon population", "pos": ["DT", "CD", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "DATE", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "28": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "678", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "29": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "1,237", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "161": [{"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "their", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "4": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Former presidential candidate Mitt Romney", "pos": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Romney", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Romney", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "I", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Romney's", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mitt Romney's", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Romney", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Romney", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Romney", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}], "8": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Facebook", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "96": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the 2012 Republican nominee", "pos": ["DT", "CD", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "DATE", "MISC", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "122": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The goal for Mr Romney", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"]}], "124": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a political street fight at an open Republican convention", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "125": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an open Republican convention", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "126": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Massachusetts", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "129": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The former Massachusetts governor", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "His", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "59": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "racism, misogyny, bigotry, xenophobia, vulgarity", "pos": ["NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "57": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "its leader", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "56": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the calculated statements of its leader", "pos": ["DT", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "51": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a contest between Trumpism and Republicanism", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "its", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "50": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republicanism", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "52": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Trumpism and Republicanism", "pos": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "MISC"]}], "199": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Graham", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}], "195": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Utah Lindsey Graham of South Carolina", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "194": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mike Lee of Utah Lindsey Graham of South Carolina", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "197": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Senate", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Senate", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "191": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Popular North Carolina Governor Nikki Haley and senators Mike Lee of Utah Lindsey Graham of South Carolina", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "190": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "South Carolina", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "193": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "senators Mike Lee of Utah Lindsey Graham of South Carolina", "pos": ["NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "192": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Popular North Carolina Governor Nikki Haley", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "115": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the other a bomb-throwing backbencher who has spent more time condemning his party's leadership than courting it", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "117": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his party's leadership", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "it", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "116": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "more time", "pos": ["JJR", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "111": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "One", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the face of the party's genteel establishment; the other a bomb-throwing backbencher who has spent more time condemning his party's leadership than courting it", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "PRP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "113": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the party's genteel establishment", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "81": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Tuesday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "86": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Mitt Romney's speech roundly condemning Donald Trump two weeks ago was just an opening salvo in what could be a long war against the New York businessman", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "87": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "two weeks", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["DATE", "DATE"]}], "84": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "New York", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "New York", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "143": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his latest moves", "pos": ["PRP$", "JJS", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "94": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Utah primary days away", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "RB"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O", "DURATION", "O"]}], "3": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "7": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Republican front-runner Donald Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "109": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Texas senator", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "102": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a last-ditch attempt", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "103": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his party", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the party's", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his party's", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "101": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ted Cruz in a last-ditch attempt", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "107": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "Mr Romney and the Texas senator", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "strange political bedfellows", "pos": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "38": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his controversial comments about immigrants, women and Muslims", "pos": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNPS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC"]}], "33": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "678 delegates", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "their delegates", "pos": ["PRP$", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "32": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "contests", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "31": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the most state contests and holds 678 delegates", "pos": ["DT", "RBS", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O"]}], "30": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Donald Trump, a billionaire businessman", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Donald Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a billionaire businessman", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Donald Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the New York businessman", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Trump's", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Trump's", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Donald Trump, including launching a third party campaign to challenge the New York businessman", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORDINAL", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Donald Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the New York businessman", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Trump", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "him", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Donald Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Trump", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON"]}], "36": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Muslims", "pos": ["NNPS"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "34": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the nomination", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "162": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the first ballot", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORDINAL", "O"]}], "60": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "threats and violence", "pos": ["NNS", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "61": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "threats", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "62": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "one", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "64": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "each and every one of these", "pos": ["DT", "CC", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O"]}], "65": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "each", "pos": ["DT"], "ner": ["O"]}], "178": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Many party members", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "their", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "68": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a speech", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "176": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the conservative movement", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "174": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "those of us in the conservative movement", "pos": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "173": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "morals and character", "pos": ["NNS", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "170": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an issue of party", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "182": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "more prominent Republicans", "pos": ["JJR", "JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Republicans", "pos": ["DT", "NNPS"], "ner": ["O", "MISC"]}], "183": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "their support", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "2": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ted Cruz", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "186": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a last-ditch effort", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "185": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mr Cruz in a last-ditch effort", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "188": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "North Carolina", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "189": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Nikki Haley", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "97": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the state's large Mormon population", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"]}], "99": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "his lot", "pos": ["PRP$", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "169": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the issue of Donald Trump", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "It", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an issue of morals and character", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "228": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the race in Missouri", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}], "164": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a statement", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "226": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "five primaries", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O"]}], "93": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Mormon", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "224": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Missouri", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "223": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "five", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "222": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "four", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "221": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a vice-presidential nominee", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "220": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "no interest in becoming a vice-presidential nominee", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "11": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the only way to nominate a Republican", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC"]}], "10": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a Facebook post", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION", "O"]}], "13": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an open convention, in which party officials choose the nominee", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "NNS", "VB", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "12": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a Republican", "pos": ["DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "MISC"]}], "15": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "officials", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "14": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an open convention", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "17": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ohio", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ohio", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "16": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the nominee", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "18": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Trumpism", "pos": ["FW"], "ner": ["MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Trumpism", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Trumpism", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "88": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "an opening salvo in what could be a long war against the New York businessman", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "89": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a long war against the New York businessman", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "151": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "ways", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "150": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Thursday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "153": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a third party campaign", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "ORDINAL", "O", "O"]}], "157": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "first", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["ORDINAL"]}], "158": [{"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "We", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "us", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "239": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a recount", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "234": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Democrat Hillary Clinton", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "her", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}], "235": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the state's Democratic primary after her opponent Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"]}], "231": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Democratic", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "232": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Vermont", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "233": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Bernie Sanders", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "48": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the onetime Democrat", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "MISC"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Democrat", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["MISC"]}], "49": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "conservative policies", "pos": ["JJ", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "46": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "November", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "47": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Some", "pos": ["DT"], "ner": ["O"]}], "44": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a weak candidate in the general election in November", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}], "45": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the general election in November", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"]}], "42": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "women", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "40": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "immigrants, women and Muslims", "pos": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "NNPS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC"]}], "41": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "immigrants", "pos": ["NNS"], "ner": ["O"]}], "1": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "5": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas Senator Ted Cruz", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "146": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "third", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["ORDINAL"]}], "200": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "February", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "203": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the floor of the Senate", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "202": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Ted Cruz on the floor of the Senate", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "205": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the trial", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "204": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Senate", "pos": ["DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Senate", "pos": ["DT", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "140": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Mr Trump's momentum", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O"]}], "209": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Marco Rubio", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "his", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "He", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "208": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Florida", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "148": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "A group of conservatives including well-known talk radio host Erick Erickson", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the group", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "149": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "well-known talk radio host Erick Erickson", "pos": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "he", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "you", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "you", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}], "77": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Mr Romney's home state of Utah", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "its", "pos": ["PRP$"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "It", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the state's", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the state's", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "76": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Utah", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Utah", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "75": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a \"fraud\"", "pos": ["DT", "``", "NN", "''"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "74": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "a \"phoney\" and a \"fraud\"", "pos": ["DT", "``", "JJ", "''", "CC", "DT", "``", "NN", "''"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "72": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "no political experience", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "79": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "its presidential contest", "pos": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}]}, "sentences": [{"openie": [{"object": "Texas", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is Senator of", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Ted Cruz"}, {"object": "Republican", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is front-runner of", "ner": {"object": ["ORGANIZATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "Republican", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is by", "ner": {"object": ["ORGANIZATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "saying", "pos": {"object": ["VBG"], "relation": ["MD", "VB"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "will vote", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Former candidate Mitt Romney"}, {"object": "Texas Senator Ted Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["MD", "VB"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "will vote for", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Former presidential candidate Mitt Romney"}, {"object": "saying", "pos": {"object": ["VBG"], "relation": ["MD", "VB"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "will vote", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Former presidential candidate Mitt Romney"}, {"object": "Texas", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is for", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Ted Cruz"}, {"object": "Texas Senator Ted Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["MD", "VB"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "will vote for", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Former candidate Mitt Romney"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Facebook post", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "said in", "ner": {"object": ["ORGANIZATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Governor John Kasich", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "campaigned with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "Governor John Kasich in Ohio", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "campaigned with", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "Ohio", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "John Kasich"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "leaders coalescing around Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "other Republican leaders coalescing", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "other leaders coalescing around Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "other leaders coalescing", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "Republican leaders coalescing", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS", "VBG"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "leaders coalescing", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "VBG"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "other Republican leaders coalescing around Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "Republican leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "other leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "leaders", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG", "IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "coalescing around", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "other Republican leaders"}, {"object": "Republican leaders coalescing around Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG", "IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "coalescing around", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "other leaders"}, {"object": "other Republican leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "joins", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "He"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG", "IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "coalescing around", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "Republican leaders"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG", "IN"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "coalescing around", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "nomination", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["CD"]}, "relation": "win", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER"]}, "subject": "1,237"}, {"object": "678 delegates", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "holds", "ner": {"object": ["NUMBER", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "contests"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "concerned", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "general election in November", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["NN", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "general election", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["NN", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "election", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["JJ", "NN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "weak candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "November", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "general election"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in general election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "him candidate in election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "him candidate in general election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "general election", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["JJ", "NN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "weak candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "However concerned", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNS"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "leaders"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in general election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "him weak candidate", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "election in November", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["JJ", "NN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "weak candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "him candidate", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "him candidate", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "him candidate in election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "him weak candidate", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "general election in November", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["JJ", "NN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "weak candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "However concerned", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "Republican leaders"}, {"object": "him candidate in general election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "him candidate in election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "election in November", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["NN", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "concerned", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "O"]}, "subject": "Republican leaders"}, {"object": "him candidate in general election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "election", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["NN", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "candidate in", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "him"}, {"object": "him candidate in election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "him candidate in general election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "general election", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "him weak candidate"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in general election in November", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his comments"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}, {"object": "him weak candidate in general election", "pos": {"object": ["PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "make", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "his controversial comments"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "conservative policies", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNP"]}, "relation": "implement", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "MISC"]}, "subject": "onetime Democrat"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "calculated statements of its leader", "pos": {"object": ["VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ", "VBN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has become Through", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, "subject": "Trumpism"}, {"object": "calculated statements", "pos": {"object": ["VBN", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ", "VBN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has become Through", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, "subject": "Trumpism"}, {"object": "statements", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ", "VBN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has become Through", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, "subject": "Trumpism"}, {"object": "statements of its leader", "pos": {"object": ["NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ", "VBN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has become Through", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["ORGANIZATION"]}, "subject": "Trumpism"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "repulsed", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "am", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "I"}, {"object": "each", "pos": {"object": ["DT"], "relation": ["VBP", "VBN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "am repulsed by", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "I"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "speech", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["RBR"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "Earlier gave", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "speech", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "gave", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "home state of Utah", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Romney"}, {"object": "its presidential contest", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "holds", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney 's home state"}, {"object": "its contest", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN"]}, "relation": "holds", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney 's home state"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "speech", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mitt Romney"}, {"object": "ago opening salvo could war", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago opening salvo", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "just opening salvo could long war", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago opening salvo", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago just opening salvo could long war", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "opening salvo could war", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago just opening salvo could war", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago just opening salvo could long war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "just opening salvo could long war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago opening salvo could long war", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago just opening salvo could war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago opening salvo could long war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago opening salvo could war", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago opening salvo could long war", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "just opening salvo", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago just opening salvo could war", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "opening salvo could war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "opening salvo", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago opening salvo could war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago just opening salvo could long war", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "just opening salvo could war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "opening salvo could long war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "ago just opening salvo", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago just opening salvo", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago just opening salvo could war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago opening salvo could long war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "just opening salvo could war", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago just opening salvo could long war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "two weeks ago opening salvo could war against New York businessman", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["DATE", "DATE", "DATE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}, {"object": "opening salvo could long war", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "was", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Donald Trump"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "last-ditch attempt", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Ted Cruz"}, {"object": "Trumpism", "pos": {"object": ["FW"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN"]}, "relation": "stop", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "personal ballot"}, {"object": "Trumpism", "pos": {"object": ["FW"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "stop", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "ballot"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "certainly bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "strange bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "strange political bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "certainly strange political bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "JJ"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "certainly strange political bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "certainly strange bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["NNS"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["JJ", "JJ"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "strange political bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "certainly bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "certainly political bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "political bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["JJ"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "strange bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "certainly political bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "JJ"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "certainly strange bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "Texas senator", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["JJ", "NNS"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "political bedfellows", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}, {"object": "bedfellows", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "are", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mr Romney"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "his party 's leadership", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "condemning", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "time"}, {"object": "face", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["CD"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER"]}, "subject": "One"}, {"object": "his party 's leadership", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["JJR", "NN"]}, "relation": "condemning", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "more time"}, {"object": "genteel establishment", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "of", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "party"}, {"object": "party 's establishment", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["CD"]}, "relation": "is face of", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER"]}, "subject": "One"}, {"object": "leadership", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "party"}, {"object": "party 's genteel establishment", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["CD"]}, "relation": "is face of", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["NUMBER"]}, "subject": "One"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "political street fight at open convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight at Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight at open Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight at open convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight at convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at open Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight at open Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at open Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at open convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at open convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight at Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "political street fight at convention", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "continues", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}, {"object": "street fight at Republican convention", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "goal"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Mr Trump 's other opponent", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "knife"}, {"object": "other opponent", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Trump"}, {"object": "all-in", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "going", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "knife"}, {"object": "all-in with Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "going", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "knife"}, {"object": "Ohio", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is Governor of", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "John Kasich"}, {"object": "John Kasich", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "'s opponent is", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Trump"}, {"object": "Ohio", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["LOCATION"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "John Kasich"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "little", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["PRP$", "NNS"]}, "relation": "prior did", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "His efforts"}, {"object": "momentum", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Trump"}, {"object": "little", "pos": {"object": ["JJ"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["PRP$", "NNS"]}, "relation": "did", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "His efforts"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "seen", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "remains", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "It"}, {"object": "seen", "pos": {"object": ["VBN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "be", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "It"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Thursday", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "met on", "ner": {"object": ["DATE"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "group"}, {"object": "ways", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "discuss", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "group"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "statement", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "said in", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "misgiving", "pos": {"object": ["VBG"], "relation": ["VBP", "RB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have also", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Many party members"}, {"object": "Republican leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has and publicly denounced", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG", "IN"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "misgiving about", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Many party members"}, {"object": "Republican leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has denounced", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "Republican leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ", "RB"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has repeatedly and denounced", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "leaders", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has denounced", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "leaders", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ", "RB"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has repeatedly and denounced", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "leaders", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has and denounced", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBG", "IN"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "misgiving about", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "party members"}, {"object": "misgiving about Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP", "RB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have also", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Many party members"}, {"object": "misgiving", "pos": {"object": ["VBG"], "relation": ["VBP", "RB"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have also", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "party members"}, {"object": "misgiving about Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "party members"}, {"object": "misgiving about Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Many party members"}, {"object": "leaders", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has and publicly denounced", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "Republican leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ", "RB"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has repeatedly and publicly denounced", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "Republican leaders", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has and denounced", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "misgiving", "pos": {"object": ["VBG"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "party members"}, {"object": "leaders", "pos": {"object": ["NNS"], "relation": ["VBZ", "RB"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "has repeatedly and publicly denounced", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "he"}, {"object": "misgiving about Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP", "RB"], "subject": ["NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have also", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O"]}, "subject": "party members"}, {"object": "misgiving", "pos": {"object": ["VBG"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["JJ", "NN", "NNS"]}, "relation": "have", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Many party members"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "their support", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["VBP", "VBG"], "subject": ["JJR", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "are throwing", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "MISC"]}, "subject": "more prominent Republicans"}, {"object": "their support", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["VBP", "VBG"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "are throwing", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "MISC"]}, "subject": "prominent Republicans"}, {"object": "their support", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["JJR", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "However are throwing", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "MISC"]}, "subject": "more prominent Republicans"}, {"object": "last-ditch effort", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "NN"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON"]}, "subject": "Cruz"}, {"object": "their support", "pos": {"object": ["PRP$", "NN"], "relation": ["RB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "However are throwing", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "MISC"]}, "subject": "prominent Republicans"}, {"object": "Mr Trump", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "stop", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "MISC"]}, "subject": "prominent Republicans"}, {"object": "Mr Trump", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["JJR", "JJ", "NNS"]}, "relation": "stop", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "MISC"]}, "subject": "more prominent Republicans"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "South Carolina", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is of", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Utah Lindsey Graham"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "have endorsed", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Popular North Carolina Governor Nikki Haley"}, {"object": "Mr Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP", "RB"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "have recently endorsed", "ner": {"object": ["O", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O", "DATE"], "subject": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Popular North Carolina Governor Nikki Haley"}, {"object": "Utah Lindsey Graham", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is of", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Mike Lee"}, {"object": "North Carolina", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["NNP", "NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Nikki Haley"}, {"object": "North Carolina", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is Governor of", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Nikki Haley"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Senate", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "was in", "ner": {"object": ["ORGANIZATION"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "trial"}, {"object": "Ted Cruz", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "kill", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "you"}, {"object": "Ted Cruz on floor", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "kill", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "you"}, {"object": "Ted Cruz on floor of Senate", "pos": {"object": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBP"], "subject": ["PRP"]}, "relation": "kill", "ner": {"object": ["PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "you"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Florida", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["LOCATION"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Marco Rubio"}, {"object": "Florida", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is Senator of", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Marco Rubio"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "Missouri", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "race"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "state 's primary Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "narrowly won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's primary after her opponent Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "narrowly won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's Democratic primary after her opponent Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "narrowly won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's Democratic Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "narrowly won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's Democratic Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's Democratic primary after her opponent Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "Vermont", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is Senator of", "ner": {"object": ["LOCATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Bernie Sanders"}, {"object": "state 's primary Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "recount", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "pursue", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "Democrat", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["NNP"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is", "ner": {"object": ["MISC"], "relation": ["MISC"], "subject": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's Democratic primary Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "narrowly won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's Democratic primary Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "Democratic primary after opponent Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["POS"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "has", "ner": {"object": ["MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "state"}, {"object": "state 's Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["RB", "VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "narrowly won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}, {"object": "state 's primary after her opponent Vermont Senator Bernie Sanders decline", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "POS", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN"], "relation": ["VBD"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "won", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "MISC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["MISC", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}, "subject": "Democrat Hillary Clinton"}]}]}