{"corefs": {"25": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a bucket in the lane with 2.7 seconds", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "26": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the lane with 2.7 seconds", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "27": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "2.7 seconds", "pos": ["CD", "NNS"], "ner": ["DURATION", "DURATION"]}], "20": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Friday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "21": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "night", "pos": ["NN"], "ner": ["TIME"]}], "22": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "72-72", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "23": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas' Isaiah Taylor", "pos": ["NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON"]}], "46": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a second-round game", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "44": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas A&M on Sunday", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "DATE"]}], "45": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Sunday", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["DATE"]}], "28": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the game", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "43": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "Northern Iowa advances", "pos": ["JJ", "NNP", "NNS"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "O"]}], "40": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the Panthers' celebration", "pos": ["DT", "NNPS", "POS", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "41": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the Panthers'", "pos": ["DT", "NNPS", "POS"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}], "1": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "75", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "3": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "72", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "final", "pos": ["JJ"], "ner": ["O"]}], "2": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "6", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "6", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "4": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Paul Jesperson", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON", "PERSON"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Jesperson, who heaved it up before the buzzer from just behind the halfcourt line", "pos": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Jesperson", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["PERSON"]}], "7": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "75-72", "pos": ["CD"], "ner": ["NUMBER"]}], "6": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas'", "pos": ["NNP", "POS"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "O"]}], "9": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Oklahoma City", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "8": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "NCAA", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION"]}], "12": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "72, final", "pos": ["CD", ",", "JJ"], "ner": ["NUMBER", "O", "O"]}], "11": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Texas Longhorns 72, final: Paul Jesperson banked in a halfcourt shot at the buzzer, and the 11th-seeded Northern Iowa Panthers upset No. 6 seed Texas 75-72 in a West Region first-round NCAA Tournament game on Friday night in Oklahoma City", "pos": ["NNP", "NNPS", "CD", ",", "JJ", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNPS", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "TIME", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "10": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Northern Iowa 75, (6) Texas Longhorns 72, final: Paul Jesperson banked in a halfcourt shot at the buzzer, and the 11th-seeded Northern Iowa Panthers upset No. 6 seed Texas 75-72 in a West Region first-round NCAA Tournament game on Friday night in Oklahoma City.", "pos": ["JJ", "NNP", "CD", ",", "-LRB-", "CD", "-RRB-", "NNP", "NNPS", "CD", ",", "JJ", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNPS", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "ner": ["O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "O", "PERSON", "PERSON", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "O", "DATE", "TIME", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Northern Iowa", "pos": ["JJ", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "it", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PRONOMINAL", "text": "it", "pos": ["PRP"], "ner": ["O"]}, {"type": "PROPER", "text": "Iowa", "pos": ["NNP"], "ner": ["LOCATION"]}], "39": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the net", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "38": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "the backboard and right", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O"]}], "15": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "a halfcourt shot at the buzzer", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "The shot", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "14": [{"type": "LIST", "text": "a halfcourt shot at the buzzer, and the 11th-seeded Northern Iowa Panthers upset No. 6 seed Texas 75-72 in a West Region first-round NCAA Tournament game", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNPS", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O"]}], "17": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "the 11th-seeded Northern Iowa Panthers upset No. 6 seed Texas 75-72 in a West Region first-round NCAA Tournament game", "pos": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNPS", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O"]}], "16": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the buzzer", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}, {"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the buzzer", "pos": ["DT", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O"]}], "19": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "a West Region", "pos": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION"]}], "18": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Iowa Panthers upset No. 6 seed Texas 75-72 in a West Region first-round NCAA Tournament game", "pos": ["NNP", "NNPS", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O", "NUMBER", "O", "LOCATION", "NUMBER", "O", "O", "LOCATION", "LOCATION", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "O", "O"]}], "36": [{"type": "PROPER", "text": "Chesapeake Energy Arena", "pos": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "ner": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}], "35": [{"type": "NOMINAL", "text": "the halfcourt line", "pos": ["DT", "NN", "NN"], "ner": ["O", "O", "O"]}]}, "sentences": [{"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "lane with 2.7 seconds", "pos": {"object": ["NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is in", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "DURATION", "DURATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bucket"}, {"object": "game", "pos": {"object": ["NN"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "tie", "ner": {"object": ["O"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bucket"}, {"object": "2.7 seconds", "pos": {"object": ["CD", "NNS"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "is with", "ner": {"object": ["DURATION", "DURATION"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "lane"}, {"object": "72-72", "pos": {"object": ["CD"], "relation": ["VB"], "subject": ["NN"]}, "relation": "tie game at", "ner": {"object": ["NUMBER"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["O"]}, "subject": "bucket"}]}, {"openie": []}, {"openie": [{"object": "on Chesapeake Energy Arena", "pos": {"object": ["IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP"], "relation": ["VBD", "IN"], "subject": ["NNPS", "POS", "NN"]}, "relation": "was on", "ner": {"object": ["O", "O", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"], "relation": ["O", "O"], "subject": ["O", "O", "O"]}, "subject": "Panthers ' celebration"}]}, {"openie": [{"object": "Sunday", "pos": {"object": ["NNP"], "relation": ["IN"], "subject": ["NNP", "NNP"]}, "relation": "is on", "ner": {"object": ["DATE"], "relation": ["O"], "subject": ["ORGANIZATION", "ORGANIZATION"]}, "subject": "Texas A&M"}]}]}